Contact

startverywell@gmail.com

live:.cid.60653e81c9b17a0 0 (Skype ID)

Top Skills

React.js PHP

Full-Stack Development

Albert Cal.

Senior Full stack developerLos Angeles

Summary

I am a experienced Web Developer with a demonstratedhistory of working in the Computer Software industry. Skilled in React, Angular, Vue, Node, AWS, Django, ASP.NET, Javascript, Python, and many frameworks and technologies. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science. Skill Sets.

Frontend web development skills

- React, Redux, Hook, Gatsby, Next.js, Vue
- HTML/XTHML, CSS
- jQuery/JavaScript
- Bootstrap, TailWind, Material CSS
- Converting Photoshop file into Web pages
- Cross browser testing in all major browsers
- Mobile responsive

Backend Web development skills

- AWS
- Node.js
- Laravel
- ASP.NET/ASP.NET Core
- Python/Django
- MySQL database

Cryptocurrency/Blockchain development skills

- Cryptocurrency exchange platform (Adding Altcoin/Trading view/ sell & buy order)
- Whole ICO development(ERC20 token/ token wallet/ ICO platform / DApp)
- Cryptocurrency Artificial Intelligence Trading Bot (Lending BOT)

Coin fork, Create Altcoin, Coin explorer, Mining pool, QT wallets(Windows/Linux)

API Development (just some of the APIs that I have worked with)

- eProcessing
- NMI
- Infusionsoft
- Konnektive

Web Hosting Administrator

- SSL, LPIC and Novell certification
- MySQL, Postgresql, Oracle, MongoDB, Apache, Nginx, AWS, RabbitMQ, Redis, Radius, ElasticSearch, Sendmail, Tomcat ...

Experience

AdviNOW Medical Senior Blockchain Engineer February 2018 - Present (3 years 10 months) California, United States

- Worked with 3+ huge companies for helping them launch web / Blockchain services
- Worked as a senior Blockchain developer
- Always give importance to TDD(Test-Driven development)

 Working from art generation, to website design + development, web3
 integration, smart contracts, airdrops, marketing, community management,
 opensea listing, etc to improve engagement.

https://boredapeyachtclub.com https://bitkong.com

Hudnu

Full Stack Engineer

April 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 10 months)

A fabulous programmer can dramatically improve your project, a poor one might create logic bombs, which may explode immediately or lay in wait for another day.

Built numerous large-scale RoR, Python and MERN, MEAN Websites on the freelancer platform.

Previous works.

- https://dev.udoobie.com
- http://fretzealot.com/
- https://www.paddingtonhotels.com/

AiRo Digital Labs Frontend Web Developer April 2012 - January 2016 (3 years 10 months) Chicago, Illinois, United States

- Created a web service that connects Django's default DB with a separate CRM system. That's was made

via SOAP requests and WSDL service from our side.

Optimized DB queries so managers can quickly download users reports. Most of the SQL queries was

made in triggers and procedures to increase response time.

 Ecommerce projects with React, Angular, AWS, Node, Laravel for petrol services, POS system https://petrolprices.com

Education

University of California, Los Angeles Bachelors, Computer Science (2008 - 2012)